<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" ?>
<Defs>
	<RulePackDef>
		<defName>ABooks_TomeOfFire_Description</defName>
		<include>
			<li>ArtDescriptionUtility_Global</li>
		</include>
		<rulePack>
			<rulesStrings>
				<!-- Roots -->
				<li>desc->[intro] [conceptExploration]. [writingQuality][ending]</li>
				<li>desc->[conceptExploration]. [writingQuality] [useWarning][ending]</li>
				<li>desc->[intro] [conceptExploration]. [writingQuality][ending]</li>
				<li>desc->[conceptExploration]. [useWarning][ending]</li>
				<li>ending->\n\nOnce read, this book will grant the reader a random fire ability with charges, and then it will be destroyed.</li>
				<!-- Introductory statements -->
				<li>intro->An Archotech relic of staggering complexity,</li>
				<li>intro->Forged in the fires of forgotten Archotech foundries,</li>
				<li>intro->A crystalline interface housing quantum flame patterns,</li>
				<li>intro->Encoded in the language of post-singularity entities,</li>
				<li>intro->Whispered to be the source of legendary infernos,</li>
				<li>intro->Recovered from a ruined vault of impossible design,</li>
				<li>intro->Deemed incomprehensible by mortal minds,</li>
				<!-- Concept Exploration -->
				<li>conceptExploration->this tome channels controlled plasma via neural mechanites</li>
				<li>conceptExploration->it unlocks the ability to summon localized heat anomalies</li>
				<li>conceptExploration->it integrates advanced pyrotechnic capabilities into its user</li>
				<li>conceptExploration->it generates self-sustaining fusion embers</li>
				<li>conceptExploration->this device allows manipulation of plasma-bound energy fields</li>
				<li>conceptExploration->it bends thermodynamic laws to project incendiary constructs</li>
				<li>conceptExploration->it encodes destructive fire patterns into a colonist’s neural link</li>
				<!-- Writing Quality by Book Quality -->
				<li>writingQuality(quality==0)->A damaged and degraded relic, its fire functions barely flicker and may malfunction.</li>
				<li>writingQuality(quality==1)->An incomplete artifact, it offers limited fire control, though it is unstable.</li>
				<li>writingQuality(quality==2)->A basic but functional tome, offering modest flame manipulation capabilities.</li>
				<li>writingQuality(quality==3)->A capable tool for fire projection, balanced between power and control.</li>
				<li>writingQuality(quality==4)->An impressive artifact, with powerful and precise pyrotechnic integration.</li>
				<li>writingQuality(quality==5)->A masterpiece of Archotech design, radiating near-perfect fire control.</li>
				<li>writingQuality(quality==6)->A flawless creation, a pinnacle of Archotech ingenuity, its power unmatched and its control absolute.</li>
				<!-- Use Warning -->
				<li>useWarning->Handle with care: prolonged use may destabilize neural pathways.</li>
				<li>useWarning->Unpredictable when used without proper cybernetic augmentation.</li>
				<li>useWarning->Potentially catastrophic in untrained hands.</li>
				<li>useWarning->Overuse may lead to uncontrolled thermodynamic feedback loops.</li>
			</rulesStrings>
		</rulePack>
	</RulePackDef>
</Defs>