<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<LanguageData>
	<ABooks_SkillLearnFactor>Skill learn factor for</ABooks_SkillLearnFactor>
	<ABooks_NotTallied> (Not tallied) </ABooks_NotTallied>
	<ABooks_ForADay>for a day</ABooks_ForADay>
	<ABooks_ForXDays>for {0} days</ABooks_ForXDays>
	<ABooks_RandomInspiration>Reader will receive a random inspiration.</ABooks_RandomInspiration>
	<ABooks_ExtraMood>Reader will receive a mood bonus of {0} for {1}.</ABooks_ExtraMood>
	<ABooks_Ability>Reader will get the {0} ability.</ABooks_Ability>
	<ABooks_Ability_Charges>Reader will get {1} charges of the {0} ability.</ABooks_Ability_Charges>
	<ABooks_Ability_Several>Reader will get one of the following abilities: {0}.</ABooks_Ability_Several>
	<ABooks_Ability_Several_Charges>Reader will get one of the following abilities: {0} with {1} charges.</ABooks_Ability_Several_Charges>
	<ABooks_ReligiousMoodImpact>Reader will receive a mood bonus or penalty, depending on whether their ideo shares the book's subject as an ideological structure.</ABooks_ReligiousMoodImpact>
	<ABooks_Hediff>Reader will receive {0} for {1}</ABooks_Hediff>
	<ABooks_HediffNoTime>Reader will receive {0}</ABooks_HediffNoTime>
	<ABooks_Nothing>This ruined book won't provide any benefit to the reader except a meager amount of recreation, and it will basically disintegrate after being read.</ABooks_Nothing>
	<ABooks_NewMapLocations>Reading this book will discover {0} new map locations on the world map.</ABooks_NewMapLocations>
	<ABooks_UnlockPsycast>Reading this book will unlock the {0} psycast (level {1}) for the reader.</ABooks_UnlockPsycast>
	<ABooks_Biome>Reading this book will give advantages to the reader when on the {0} biome.</ABooks_Biome>
	<ABooks_StatsReport_TempMinByBiome>In the {0} biome: -20 ºC</ABooks_StatsReport_TempMinByBiome>
	<ABooks_StatsReport_TempMaxByBiome>In the {0} biome: +20 ºC</ABooks_StatsReport_TempMaxByBiome>
	<ABooks_StatsReport_MultiplierByBiome>In the {0} biome: +20 %</ABooks_StatsReport_MultiplierByBiome>
	<ABooks_CallRaids>Reader will learn some... very creative insults for an enemy faction, which will entice them to raid the colony with {0}x strength.</ABooks_CallRaids>
	<ABooks_RandomAstronomicalIncident>Through an unknown mechanism, reading this book will trigger a random astronomical incident.</ABooks_RandomAstronomicalIncident>
	<ABooks_Nonsense>The text is nonsensical and nearly unreadable. It is a mystery what effect reading it may have, if any.</ABooks_Nonsense>
	<ABooks_StainlessSteel>Studying this treatise unlocks stainless steel as a material, enabling its crafting and use in construction and crafting projects. Anything created out of steel by the reader will from now on be made with stainless steel instead, which has better qualities and is non-flammable.</ABooks_StainlessSteel>
	<ABooks_DurathreadTechniques>Studying this treatise unlocks durathread as a material, enabling its crafting and use in construction and crafting projects. Anything created out of cloth by the reader will from now on be made with durathread instead, which has better qualities.</ABooks_DurathreadTechniques>
	
	<Abooks_DisableQuests>Disable Ruined Library quests</Abooks_DisableQuests>
	<Abooks_DisableQuests_Description>Disables Ruined Library quests from triggering. Bear in mind these quests are independent of any other quests or storyteller events (raids, manhunters, etc).</Abooks_DisableQuests_Description>
	<Abooks_QuestRate>Ruined Library quests multiplier (lower means getting the event more often)</Abooks_QuestRate>
	<Abooks_QuestRateTooltip>The frequency of the Ruined Library quest being offered is multiplied by this number (with a multiplier of 1, it is offered every between 15 and 30 days at random). Numbers below 1 decrease the time, while numbers above it increase it. Note that this event doesn't "replace" normal quests, it works independently.</Abooks_QuestRateTooltip>
	<Abooks_Reset>Reset</Abooks_Reset>
</LanguageData>